(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-28T09:39:21.345690",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
hololive 3rd generation live きゅるるん大作戦 〜最強アイドル、推しちゃいなさい！〜
hololive 3rd generation live: Kyururun Operation ~Ultimate Idols, Totally Fan For Us!~
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: To All Attendees
2次販売グッズ
2nd Release Merchandise
アクリルパネル
Acrylic Panel
だから きみのこと
Because I love you so much,
好き好き好き好き大好きずっと
love, love, love, love, loving you always,
あふれるこの
overflowing with this
きっと
surely
たまらない
irresistible
アイアイアイアイ アイラビュー
i-i-i-i-i love you
あいあいあいあい♪ 愛にゅう？
Ai-ai-ai-ai♪ Ain't you?
もっと！ もっと！
More! More!
いなくなって 愛させて！
Let me love you!
夢見るハートが ぴょんぴょんぴょん！
My dreaming heart goes pyon-pyon-pyon!
あんなに落ちて あみゃあみゃ
Falling so hard, amya-amya
こんなになっても いまだ抜け出せない！
Even like this, I still can't escape!
どうしたもんかの ぬ い ぬ い ぬ い！
What should I do, nui-nui-nui!
すきなだけ 愛してね！
Just love me as much as you like!
アニメにハマって
Getting into anime,
歌いたくなっちゃった
I just wanted to sing!
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて...
Singing karaoke while watching my favorite scenes...
尊すぎて辛いっ！
It's too precious, it hurts!
歌いたいアニソン・ゲーソン見つけよう！
Let's find anime songs we want to sing!
JOYSOUND
吉野家でごはんしょ♪
Have a meal at Yoshinoya!
本日は、ホロライブ
Today, Hololive...
ホロライブ 3rd Generation Live
Hololive 3rd Generation Live
キュるん大作戦 最強アイドルお寿司かないでしょ!にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます!
Thank you for attending Kyurun Great Operation: The Ultimate Idol Is the Only Way!
最後までライブをお楽しみいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the concert until the very end, we have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影・録音・録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
The use of filming, recording, or photography equipment during the performance is strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮ください。
Smoking is prohibited inside the building. Please refrain from smoking.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
If you happen to feel unwell, please don't push yourself and notify a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他のみんなの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね!
Mosh pits, diving, throwing objects onto the stage, and any behavior that inconveniences others or disrupts the show are strictly prohibited. Please follow the rules and enjoy!
また本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合があります。
Also, video streaming and photography cameras will be inside the venue, and audience seats may be captured.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がありますので、あらかじめご容赦ください。
These images and videos may be used for promotional purposes, so please understand this in advance.
またライブのハッシュタグは #キュるん大作戦DAY2 です。ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください!
Also, the live hashtag is #KyurunGreatOperationDAY2. Please use the hashtag to hype things up!
それでは開演まであと少しです。君たちの声をいっぱい聞かせてください!
Well then, the show is about to begin. Let us hear your loud voices!
そして、今からちょっと三期生でエンジンを組もうと思っているんですが、えっと、マイクを通さずやりますので、ちょっと静かにして、耳をすませて聞いていただきまして……
And now, the 3rd Gen members are going to huddle up together. Since we won't be using microphones for this, please quiet down and listen closely...
欲張りな電脳ガール
Greedy cyber girl,
どこへ行くの？
where are you going?
夢の続き見せてよ
Show me the continuation of the dream.
秘密のコードを入力して
Enter the secret code,
扉を開けたら始まっちゃうよ
open the door, and it all begins!
キミと私の共通点
The common ground between you and me—
見つけてしまったのなら
if we've already found it,
もう逃げられない！
there's no escaping anymore!
画面越しじゃ物足りない
Through the screen is not enough,
こっちに来てよ darling
come over here, darling!
トキメキの魔法にかけて
Cast a spell of excitement,
もっと夢を見させてよ
and let me dream even more!
準備はいいかい？
Are you ready?
もっと盛り上がってこ！
Let's get even more hyped!
欲張りな電脳ガール
Greedy cyber girl,
まだ終わらない
it's not over yet,
キミの声を聞かせてよ
let me hear your voice,
もっともっと！
more and more!
デジタルな世界だって
Even in a digital world,
キミがいれば最強なんだ
with you here, we're unstoppable!
最高の瞬間を
This greatest moment
一緒に刻もうよ
let's etch it together!
ラストスパートだよ！
It's the final spurt!
欲張りな電脳ガール
Greedy cyber girl,
止まらない！
there's no stopping!
キミと描くストーリー
The story we weave with you
ずっと永遠に…！
will last for eternity...!
超アイドル！
Super idol!
電脳ガールはよくばり
The virtual girl is greedy,
笑いあって もっとかわいくなる
Laugh together, becoming even cuter
Oh yeah, yeah
遠いようで近くて
Feels far but actually close,
他人なのに家族みたいで
even though we're strangers, it's like family.
ラグのないカンバセーション
A conversation without lags,
グルらないセンセーション
a sensation that doesn't go around.
喜怒哀楽をシェアしてさ
Sharing joys, anger, sadness, and fun,
でっかくなっていきたいよね？
we want to grow big, right?
でもちっちゃなことも大事にして
But also cherish the small things,
一つ一つ刻んでく
carving each moment carefully.
楽しんでくれるのが楽しい
It's fun when you enjoy it,
根っからのエンターテイナー
a true entertainer at heart.
後ろまで見えてる
I can see all the way to the back,
画面の向こうも届いてる
it reaches even beyond the screen.
光の海を泳ぐの
Swimming through a sea of light,
超アイドル！
super idol!
電脳ガールはよくばり
The virtual girl is greedy,
愛されたいし 夢だって見たい 君とじゃなきゃやだ！
I want to be loved, and I want to dream too — only with you!
絶好調です 狙い撃ちで君にウィンク
Feeling at my best, taking aim and winking at you.
やっぱり電脳ガールで めっちゃハッピー
After all, being a virtual girl is super happy,
あれもしたいし これもしたいし
I want to do this, I want to do that—
叶えちゃうやっだー！
everything comes true, yay!
先頭走る もちろん君と
Running at the front, of course with you,
笑いあって もっとかわいくなる
laughing together, becoming even cuter.
Oh yeah, yeah
せっかくだからやりきりたい
Since we have the chance, I want to do it all,
でも乗り越えるべき壁もでかい
but the walls we must overcome are huge.
トライアンドエンタメです
Try and entertain,
君が思ってるよりずっと君のこと想ってる
I'm thinking of you much more than you realize.
どうかな？ (Fu-fu)
How is it? (Fu-fu)
焦がれた夢には (Fu-fu)
I've longed for it (Fu-fu)
近づけてるかな？ (Fu-fu)
Am I getting closer to my dream? (Fu-fu)
声の波があるから 頑張れるんだ
The waves of voices give me strength — let me hear them.
聞かせて！ (1, 2, 3, 4)
(One, two, three, four)
もう最高！
This is the best!
電脳ガールは幸せ
The virtual girl is happy,
愛されていて 伸びしろあって 下向くとかやだ！
loved and growing — never looking down!
テンポアップし続けていく
Continuing to speed up the tempo
見たい景色へ
towards the scenery I want to see.
世界満たす (Love and peace, love and peace)
Fill the world (Love and peace, love and peace)
喧騒より断然 (Love and peace, love and peace)
Definitely more than fighting (Love and peace, love and peace)
今すぐ達成 (Love and peace, love and peace)
Achieve it right now (Love and peace, love and peace)
みんなで作っていく (Yeah!)
Creating it together (Yeah!)
自信揺らいでも頑張っちゃう
Even if my confidence shakes, I'll keep trying,
褒められて伸びる 分かってるよね？
I grow when praised — you know that, right?
この空間が宝物
This space is a treasure,
泣いしちゃわないよ 笑う
I won't cry, I'll smile.
(君と一緒に！ 超アイドル！)
(Together with you, super idol!)
電脳ガールはよくばり
The virtual girl is greedy,
愛されたいし 夢だって見たい 君とじゃなきゃやだ！
I want to be loved, and I want to dream too — only with you!
絶好調です 狙い撃ちで君にウィンク
Feeling at my best, taking aim and winking at you.
やっぱり電脳ガールで めっちゃハッピー
After all, being a virtual girl is super happy,
あれもしたいし これもしたいし
I want to do this, I want to do that—
叶えちゃうやっだー！
everything comes true, yay!
先頭走る もちろん君と
Running at the front, of course with you,
笑いあって もっとかわいくなる
laughing together, becoming even cuter.
どこまででも行けそうな気がする
I feel like I can go anywhere.
Oh yeah, yeah
初めて出会った日 今でも覚えてる
The day we first met, I still remember it.
魔法にかかられたみたい 輝きだした ah
It's like I was put under a spell, and started to shine, ah.
同じスタートから 一歩一歩
From the same start, step by step,
そう同じ夢を描いてきた仲間 yeah
friends who have drawn the same dream, yeah.
ずっと一緒に歩いてきたんだね
We've been walking together all this time.
君と一緒に！
Together with you!
喜びも涙もわけあって 新しい景色を見にいこうよ
Sharing joys and tears, let's go see new scenery.
さあ手をつないで stay together
Now let's hold hands, stay together.
いつでもまっすぐな 頑張る君が好き
I love how you always work so straight and hard.
明るい優しさに癒されてありがとう ah
Thank you for healing me with your bright kindness, ah.
心が折れそうな時にはそっと
When my heart is about to break, softly...
そうみんなを導いてくれる君は素敵
You're wonderful for guiding everyone.
きっと何より強い絆だから どんな壁も乗り越えていけるよ
Because our bond is stronger than anything, we can overcome any wall.
これからも続けていきたいな わたしたちの story
I want to keep continuing our story.
たくさんの幻想が溢れるこの世界で 巡り集まる奇跡 確かな現実
In this world overflowing with fantasies, miracles gathering together become reality.
今日はこのままさよならじゃないよ 手をとってくれたなら
Today isn't a final goodbye, if you take my hand.
秘密も眠りにつくような夜に 君を連れてくよ
I'll take you to a night where even secrets fall asleep.
それは例えば遠く離れてたって 手を繋いでいられるような
Even if we're far apart, like being able to hold hands,
奇跡のような話をしよう
Let's talk about a miraculous story.
まずはドアを開けといて
First, keep the door open.
今日までの思い出して 一つ一つ並べたら
Remembering up until today, lining them up one by one,
明日の雨粒が気になり出して
tomorrow's raindrops start to weigh on my mind.
とも眠れないみたいだ 変わりたいことや 変わらなきゃいけないことも
It seems like I can't sleep either. Things I want to change, and things I must change,
少しは進めた ママ窓の外 眺めていたんだ
I've moved forward a little, gazing outside the window.
雨が降り出すその前に 君のところまで 行けるような気がして
Before the rain starts falling, I feel like I can go all the way to where you are.
目を閉じて見失ったんだ そのまま遠くへと 行こう
Closing my eyes, I lost sight of it, let's go far away just like that.
手をとってくれるかな 秘密も眠りにつくような夜を
Will you take my hand? A night where even secrets fall asleep,
君と泳いでいくよ 街の灯りが消えるたびに笑って
I'll swim with you, smiling every time the town's lights go out.
雨が降り出すその前に 君のところまで 行けるような気がして
Before the rain starts falling, I feel like I can go to where you are.
目を閉じて見失ったんだ
Closing my eyes, I lost sight of it.
そのまま遠くへと行こう 手をとってくれるかな
Let's go far away just like that, will you take my hand?
秘密も眠りにつくような夜を 君とおよいでいくよ
A night where even secrets fall asleep, I'll swim with you.
街の灯りが消えるたびに笑って 路地裏で抱き合おう
Laughing every time the town lights fade, let's embrace in the alleyway.
まあとはあけいといて 話をしよう
Leave the door open, let's talk.
まあとはあけいといて 聞こえる聞こえる
Leave the door open, I can hear it, I can hear it.
次はマリン！ 君たち！
Next is Marine! You guys!
ぶつかれ！盛り上がっていきましょう！
Clash! Let's get hyped up!
言い訳ばかり 駄目駄目駄目
All excuses, no no no!
だってあたしが好きなのよ！
Because you love me!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
なんだかなんないかな ラビラビ
Isn't there anything we can do? Rabi-rabi,
隣のあいつが邪魔だな
That guy next to me is in the way.
いけない そんなこと だめだめだ
You mustn't, that's no good, no no.
戦略的敗北? ドアとは違うな なんだって競争？
Strategic defeat? That's totally different, what kind of competition is this?
君が出した そうゆうの なんか寂しい
You putting it like that is kind of lonely.
気持ちはチューリング 眠いしシークレット 秘密のシークレット
Feelings are Turing, sleepy and secret, a secret secret.
あの子には負けない 今だってジャラシ 逆転劇だ
I won't lose to that girl, even now teasing, it's a comeback drama!
逆転か？ してあります！
A reversal? It's already done!
言わなきゃって分かってる ああでもない こうでもない
I know I have to say it, but it's not this, not that.
やめにしましょう つらぬけ マイマイマイマイ
Let's stop it, stick to it, my-my-my-my!
聞き たく ない 言い訳 ばかり
I don't want to hear all your excuses!
時間がかかるの よジュジュダ
It takes time, Juju-da!
単純ハニバニ ダリダリ マジな話 どっちどっちが好きなのよ！
Simple honey-bunny, darlin' darlin', seriously speaking, which one do you like?!
ダメダメダメ よそ見しないで ダメダメダメ 抜け出したい
No no no, don't look away, no no no, I want to break out.
のは私の方でしょ？ どうして反対の方ワンターン？
It's me, right? Why is the opposite side one turn?
言い訳ばかり
All excuses!
言い訳ばかりに じだんだの憂鬱
Just making excuses, stomping in frustration,
普段だったハニバニ どでかいマジな話
Honey-bunny as usual, a super serious talk,
どっちが好きなのよ？
Which one do you like better?
ダメダメダメ 夜遊びしないで
No, no, no, don't stay out late!
ダメダメダメ 抜け出したい
No, no, no, I want to sneak out!
けどやるしかない
But I have no choice,
正反対の方向 ワン！ テー！
In the opposite direction, one, two!
次は、せーのっ！
Next, ready, go!
外出た瞬間終わったわ
The moment I stepped outside, it was over,
天気はいいのに進めない
The weather's nice, but I can't move forward.
風強すぎておおかなくなリ
The wind's too strong, I might disappear,
定期定期的にオールバック
Regularly, I put my hair all back.
外出た瞬間終わったわ
The moment I stepped outside, it was over,
天気はいいのに進めない
The weather's nice, but I can't move forward.
風強すぎておおかなくなリ
The wind's too strong, I might disappear,
定期定期的にオールバック
Regularly, I put my hair all back.
まだまだ楽しみたいのに
Even though I want to enjoy myself more,
でもでも時間が足りない
But there's never enough time.
ワクワクする明日へ
Toward an exciting tomorrow,
思い切って飛び切って巻き返して進もう
Taking a leap, pushing through, let's press on!
背伸びたほきで
Standing tall on tiptoes,
突き進くちゃえ
Let's charge right ahead,
最高速ゆえにpassing
Passing by at top speed,
ああもう鬱陶しい
Ah, it's so annoying,
誰だってどうせ不安だカラ
Everyone's anxious anyway,
平穏って定義しよう
Let's define it as peace and quiet.
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
It's all okay!
皆笑えばヌデキタメー
If everyone smiles, it's all good.
なんなく全力で
Effortlessly, with all my might,
突き抜けちゃって
Breaking right through,
まっすぐな気持ちで行こう
Let's go with a straight, honest feeling!
なかなか
It's not easy,
お布団から出られない日もある
Some days you just can't get out of bed.
でも明日から
But starting tomorrow,
そう明日から
Yes, starting tomorrow,
本気出すんだ
I'll get serious!
気づくまで
Until I realize,
気がくれるまで
Until I lose my mind,
根拠なきらしで
With baseless confidence,
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
It's all okay!
皆笑えばヌデキタメー
If everyone smiles, it's all good.
なんなく全力で
Effortlessly, with all my might,
突き抜けちゃって
Breaking right through,
まっすぐな気持ちで行こう
Let's go with a straight, honest feeling!
最高速ゆえにpassing
Passing by at top speed,
ああもう鬱陶しい
Ah, it's so annoying,
誰だってどうせ不安だカラ
Everyone's anxious anyway,
平穏って定義しよう
Let's define it as peace and quiet.
イッツ・オール・オッケー！
It's all okay!
皆笑えばヌデキタメー
If everyone smiles, it's all good.
なんなく全力で
Effortlessly, with all my might,
突き抜けちゃって
Breaking right through,
まっすぐな気持ちで行こう
Let's go with a straight, honest feeling!
髪の毛恐怖オールバック
The fear of hair, all back!
最後は、ノエル！
Lastly, Noel!
what's 純情？
What's pureness?
お口に合いますか？
Does it suit your taste?
甘ったるいだけじゃ満足しないね
Just being sweet isn't satisfying,
スタンバイはとっくにできてるの
We've been on standby for a long time.
wii-wii-woo
右往左往しても人間ばっか
Even going this way and that, it's just humans,
スワイプアンドタップしても
Even if you swipe and tap,
大勢影響なしでlonely
Lonely, without affecting the majority.
ああもう鬱陶しい
Ah, it's so annoying,
ノイズを浚ってよ雷鳴
Thunder, sweep away the noise!
聞いたことのない爆音で
With a roar you've never heard before,
塵みたいな埃っぽいのを一掃で黙らせたいね
I want to silence that dusty dust with one sweep.
不明瞭な声援よりでっかいのくれ
Give me something bigger than unclear cheers,
私にステージをくれ
Give me the stage!
冷淡冷徹な独裁？no way
Cold and ruthless dictatorship? No way.
必要な毒
Necessary poison,
最高沸点にこだわりたい
I want to obsess over the highest boiling point.
好きにのたまいタイナ
Say whatever you want,
独尊唯我なんて大層なこと言ってないの
I'm not saying anything as grand as 'holier-than-thou'.
適宜徹底的な刺しちゃって
Appropriately and thoroughly stabbing,
a-ha-ha
前例ないくらいに燃やしたいんだって
I want to burn it like never before,
狭い部屋の中だって
Even inside a narrow room,
心なしジンクラに膨張してるんだろ
It's swelling up somewhat dizzyingly, right?
ああもうリミットかけずにブスとして
Ah, without setting limits, looking sullen,
純情波動にも滑稽で
Comical even in pure waves,
歪なほどに光るものなの
It's something that shines the more distorted it is.
知らないならちょっと黙ろうか？
If you don't know, why don't you shut up for a second?
道を開けろよhoney
Make way, honey!
世界はもっと高ぶれる
The world can get even more excited.
wii-wii-woo
blah-blah-blah
乗るか soru か賭してるけど
I'm betting on make-or-break, but
負けるはずないな
There's no way I'll lose.
救世主の采配はたぶん気まぐれ
The savior's judgment is probably fickle,
じゃあどんな結果だって最高速ゆえにpassing
So whatever the result, passing by at top speed!
ああもう鬱陶しい
Ah, it's so annoying,
誰だってどうせ不安だなら
Everyone's anxious anyway,
平穏って定義しよう
Let's define it as peace.
灼熱にて純情
Pureness in scorching heat!
~最強アイドル、推ししかないでしょ~
~Strongest idol, push is the only way!~
レッツゲットラウダー!レッツゲットラウダー!レッツゲットラウダー!
Let's get louder! Let's get louder! Let's get louder!
じゃあ、さっそく自己紹介からしていきますか!
Now then, shall we start with self-introductions?
していきましょう!
Let's do it!
じゃあみんな、ペコらは久しぶりのあの挨拶行くから。
Alright, everyone, Pekora's going first with my traditional greeting!
わかるよね、みんなー!
You all know it, right? Everyone!
あの挨拶だよ!
That greeting!
どの挨拶だ?
That greeting?
あれだ!
That!
あれしかねぇ!
That's right!
いくぞ!
Here we go!
タダンガダン・ダン・ダン、全人類Vtuberん、全人類...
Tadanga-dan-dan-dan, all VTubers in the world, Vtuber...
え?待って待って待って待って待って!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
大丈夫か?
Are you okay?
もう一回ね!
Wait, wait, wait!
もう一回ね!いきます!
Let's do it again!
ダン!
Tan!
タダンガダン・ダン・ダン、全Vtuberイチ超絶可愛いのはだれだ!
Tadanga-dan-dan-dan, all VTubers in the world, the cutest is...
タダンガダン・ダン・ダン!
Tadanga-dan-dan-dan!
ペコラ!
Pekora!
やっとできました!ありがとうございます!
I did it! Thank you!
やったー!
Yay!
じゃあ次はフレア!
Alright, next is Flare!
はい、じゃあフレアは「はい、ダーリン」っていうので「はい、ハニー」って返してください。
Hi, darling! You have to reply with "Hi, honey!" OK?
オッケー!
OK!
いきますよ!
Here we go!
はい、ダーリン!
Hi, darling!
はい、ハニー!
Hi, honey!
ありがとうございます!
Thank you!
ホロライブ3期生のフレアです。そして?
That's Flare from Hololive 3rd Generation! And then...
はい、どうしようかな。
Yes, what should I do?
え、じゃあコンマする?って言うから普通に「コンマする!」
Should I say "Commasul"?
牛丼もね!
Or gyudon?
牛丼でもいいのか?
Is that okay?
いや、牛丼はまあ、ばっ。
Gyudon is... well, yeah.
あ、あ、やばいやばい。
Ah, oh no, oh no!
いくぞ!
Let's go!
コンマする!
Commasul!
カマする!
はい、ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルでーーす!
I'm Shirogane Noel from Hololive 3rd Generation!
きみたち!本物のぺこぺこカマするは、だれー?
And you guys, who is the real PekoPeko Comasul?
ぺこぺこカマする!ぺこぺこカマする!
PekoPeko Comasul! PekoPeko Comasul!
なんか、はじめてのくせに。
No, from the beginning...
ぺこぺこカマする!
PekoPeko Comasul!
ちょっと待って、最初からさ、白銀に船長取られるの、白銀でぺこぺこカマする?
Wait, from the beginning, Shirogane steals PekoPeko Comasul?
ぺこぺこカマする!ぺこぺこカマする!
PekoPeko Comasul! PekoPeko Comasul!
なんなのこれ?
What is this?
というわけでね。
Well, that's that.
はい、ホロライブ3期生宝鐘海賊団の船長、宝鐘マリンでーーす!
I am Houshou Marine from Hololive 3rd Generation, Houshou Pirates!
そしてついにデイク!デイク!デイク!
And finally, Deichu! Deichu!
あれ?のえると衣装近くない?
Wait, isn't that similar to Noel's?
ねえ!
Really?
わかりましたか、みなさん?昨日とちょっと...
Did you guys notice? Yesterday...
悪魔になっちゃったの。
We turned into demons!
昨日からちょっと、こう、小悪魔っぽくなっちゃったかな?
From yesterday, we became a bit more devilish, didn't we?
そうなんですよ。
That's right, you know.
実はこれ初めて公開するんですよ!
Actually, we are revealing this for the first time!
みんなびっくりしたかな?
Did everyone get surprised?
かわいい!
So cute!
ありがとうございます!
Thank you!
え、でも、悪魔...
Well, but, demon...
なんか、結構、マリンは小悪魔系で売ってるんで、かなりシナジーあるかな。
Somehow, Marine is selling herself as a little devil, so she might have more synergy.
ペコらも小悪魔系やってるからね。
Pekora is also selling herself as a little devil.
みんな小悪魔系だわ。
Everyone is a little devil!
みんな小悪魔系だから。
みんな小悪魔だから。
Everyone is a little devil!
We are all little devils.
いやいや、うちら小悪魔じゃなくて天使じゃん。え?天使だよね?
No, no, no, we're not little devils! We're angels, right?
天使か悪魔、どっちが好きなのたち?
So, are we demons or angels?
じゃあ、あいって言ってもらえれば、天使の言葉を言って。
Well, if you say "angel", then say it's an angel's words.
え、天使ライト?天使ライト?
Eh, "angel light"?
色的に、ノエルとあ、うん。
Color-wise, Flare and Noel...
色的に、あ、うん。じゃあ、悪魔派は...
Ah, and Flare...
赤、赤!
Red, red!
天使派は、白!
Angel's, white!
じゃあ、いくか。
Okay, let's go.
じゃあ、みなさん変えて、かかげてください!かかげてください!ピラモッカカゲ。
Then, everyone, please raise your penlights! Raise them, raise them!
あ、でも結構、いい感じに割れてる。
Oh, but it's splitting pretty well.
若干、赤が多いか?
Maybe red is more?
え?あれ?
Wait, red?
赤の方が人気なのかな?
Red is more popular?
赤の方があ、いやでも結構...
あ、でも半々か?
Ah, but half-half?
半々か!
Half-half!
すっげえやってるね!
They're doing it evenly!
すっげえ!ありがとうございます!
Amazing! Thank you!
え、じゃあ、今日いいね、悪魔な感じも...
So today, both the demon and...
天使な感じも、両方見せられてよかったってことだね!
Angel's is good too, right?
もちろん、デイチュは引き続き、バンドも名前もさとす!
And of course, Deichu will continue to be called Bandou!
ありがとうございます!
Thank you so much!
っと、かっこいいですね、これね！
Ah, it's so cool, isn't it!
かっこいい！
So cool!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
嬉しいですねー
We're so happy!
そうそしてね、配信のコメントももちろん見てますからね！
And of course, we're watching the stream comments too!
見てるよ！
We see you!
みんなー！もうもちろん！
Everyone! Of course!
会場のみんなももちろん！あったかいなー！
Everyone at the venue too! You guys are so warm!
めっちゃあたたかい！
So warm!
みんな素敵な気合いの入った
Everyone came in such wonderful,
推し活ファッションしてきてくれてありがとー！
enthusiastic oshi-katsu fashion, thank you!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
かわいいー！
So cute!
最高、最高ですよ。
It's the best, absolute best.
いやもうちょっぱなね、初期メドレーでしたけども。
Well, right at the start, it was the early medley, though.
よー、やば、やばかったよね。
Man, it was crazy, wasn't it?
で、ですね、なんとですね、ここまでで、え？
And, you know, surprisingly, up to this point, huh?
冒頭無料ちら見せが、
The free introductory sneak peek...
終了となります！
...has come to an end!
えー！そんなことある！？嘘でしょ！？
What?! Is that real?! No way?!
嘘ペコでしょ？
Just kidding, right?
そうなんですよ、嘘ではないペコです。
That's right, no kidding here peko.
嘘だよ
Just kidding
でも、やっぱね、みんな見たいと思ってくれてると思うから、
But since we know everyone wants to watch more,
概要欄に配信チケットのリンクがあるので、今！ぽちぽちっと、貼ってみてください。
there's a link to the stream tickets in the description, so go ahead and tap/click it right now!
ここから先は見せない！今日はすごい！
We won't show you past here! Today is amazing!
今日もまたすごいことになってます！
Today is going to be amazing again!
もう、ぶち上げぶち上げで、そう、準備はね、
With non-stop hype, yeah, the preparations...
Day 1とは違ったペコじゃん。
...were different from Day 1, peko.
盛り上がり！そう！
The excitement! Yeah!
もう、みんな、君たちも今日超ぶち上がりなんで、
Everyone, you guys are super hyped today too,
頑張って最後まで息切れしないように、ぶち上がってください！
so do your best and stay hyped all the way to the end without running out of breath!
最後まで！しっかり声出ししてね！出してね！
Right to the end! Make sure to call out loud!
そしてね、配信で楽しんでる人は、
And for those enjoying the stream,
あの配信タグ「#るるん大作戦Day2」いっぱい呟いてください！
please tweet a lot with the stream tag #るるん大作戦Day2!
呟いてね！
Tweet away!
ふう、ふう。
Phew, phew.
緊張するね。
Makes you nervous.
そろそろ？
Almost time?
いいですか？
Are you ready?
あ、行きます？次曲に行ってもいいでしょうか？
Ah, ready? Can we move on to the next song?
行きましょう！
Let's go!
はい、次の曲はなんとわたくしからスタートさせていただいた...
Yes, the next song actually starts with me...
なにがくるんだろー！
Wonder what's coming!
なんだろう！なんだろう！
What could it be?!
次の曲いきましょう！
Let's go to the next song!
キュリアメドレー！
Kuria Medley!
いぇーい！
Yay!